This is OpenPatch from the very beginning, in one uninterrupted browser recording.
OpenPatch lets people repair websites they do not own, then share that repair safely with everyone else.
First, download the extension from the public OpenPatch site.
Unzip it, open Chrome extensions, enable Developer mode, and choose Load unpacked.
This clean demo profile now shows the real OpenPatch version zero point eight extension running.
Now we open the MetroCare directory.
The original website has twelve services, but no search, no filters, and no comparison.
A person has to read every card to find accessible care in their language.
We open the actual extension on this website.
OpenPatch checks the public registry and discovers a community repair made for this exact domain and path.
It verifies the publisher policy, the patch hash, and all eleven live selector targets before offering installation.
One click installs and activates the verified feature.
This is a constrained OpenPatch document, not arbitrary JavaScript.
It may use only declared operations, and it receives access only to the website it repairs.
The page reloads with the missing feature added by the extension.
We select two real listings and open the new keyboard-accessible comparison.
The original website remains intact; OpenPatch adds a personal usability layer on top.
Next we filter for wheelchair access, Urdu, and providers accepting new patients.
Twelve cards become one useful result.
The filtering happens locally in the browser, so private preferences are not sent to MetroCare or to OpenPatch.
We reload the website.
The installed repair runs again automatically, and the unfinished filter choices are still here.
This proves that the result is a working browser feature, not a screenshot or a one-time preview.
Opening the extension again shows that the repair is active only on this website, every operation is healthy, and the permissions are reviewable.
The user can disable or remove it at any time.
Codex is needed only when someone authors and tests a new repair.
Everyone downstream simply installs the verified community patch with no AI, no account, and no API key.
That is OpenPatch: fix the web you have, and share the fix.